片名：女巫布莱尔
在1994年10月 三个电影学院学生
在马里兰州博克斯维尔地区
的森林拍摄记录片时失踪
一年后 人们找到了他们当时拍摄的胶片
- 在录了  - 好
- It's already recording...  - Okay.
这是我的家
This is my home...
- 你的样子看起来很模糊 让我把它缩小点  - 好
- You look blurry. I'll zoom out.  - Okay.
早上好
Good morning.
- 好了吗?  - 好 我可以了
- Got it?  - Okay, I got it.
这是我的家
This is my home, ...
周末我离开我的家
...which I am leaving for the weekend...
去拜访传说中的女巫布莱尔
...to investigate the Blair Witch.
如何在森林中活下来
Essential reading: "How to Stay Alive in the Woods", ...
'因为你从不知道将要发生什么
...'cause you never know what's gonna happen.
这是一本很重要的书
And this is an important book...
因为它清楚地说出了在科菲发生的事情
...because it has the article about what happened at Coffin Rock.
它看上去相当旧了
It looks pretty old...
它完全地久了 还有这是我的野外笔记本
It's totally old. And this is my field notebook.
这不是规矩先生吗！
It's Mr. Punctuality.
今早过得怎么样了?
How are you this morning?
累死了
Tired.
我让把摄像机抬起来
So I got the CP up.
不错
Good.
这就是我们用来拍摄的？
That's what we're shooting on.
不 没人知道我会拿着它 但我拿到了
No one knows I took it, but I got it.
快 进房子里 快
Come into the house. Come on.
我能看见你
I can see you.
我们不会踩到狗屎的 我现在在向后退
We're not gonna bump into shit, I'm going backwards now.
我们不能搞坏摄像机
We mustn't fuck up the cameras.
迈克在哪里?
So where's Mikey?
- 我们得去找他  - 好
- We have to go get him.  - Okay.
在8点半
At 8:30.
好
Okay.
我们的进度表已经推迟了 但重要的是我们有影液
We're already behind schedule, but it's important to have juice.
棒
That's cool.
我猜你是迈克
I guess you're Mike!
等等 停下
Wait. Stop.
我们可以和你妈妈聊会吗?
Don't we get to meet your Mama?
待会儿见 妈
See you later, Mom!
你好吗 迈克?
How are you, Mike?
我很累 但还不错
I'm tired but I'm fine.
对这次的体验我真的很兴奋 感谢上帝给我机会
I'm real excited about this. Thank you for the opportunity.
我很高兴 真幸运可以把这些设备凑齐
I'm very glad. Thanks for getting the equipment together.
我们有足够的电力和燃料
We've got enough battery power to...
供给一个小国家一个月
...fuel a small country for a month.
我们准备了米 水果冲压机
We've got rice, fruit punch...
麦片 葡萄干 宝贝
Oatmeal Raisin, baby.
最后的宿营地
The ultimate campfood.
感觉很柔软
Feel how soft.
- 棉花糖  - 你真狡猾 从我车里出去
- Marshmallows...  - Hey, you weasel. Out of my cart!
你相信有鬼吗?
Do you believe in ghosts?
女巫布莱尔的传说?
Ever heard of the Blair Witch?
听起来很熟悉 我姐姐在布莱尔高中
Sounds familiar. My sister went to Blair High School.
那片森林在圣诞节前后就像有脚 一样在爬行
The woods around Halloween are creepy.
能说详细些吗? 我不想瞎说
- Can you tell me a little more?  - I don't wanna go cheesy.
我想说得坦白些
I want to present this straightforward.
那个传说让人不安
The legend is unsettling.
想要得到
Wanna get the...
开机仪式的第一镜?
...ceremonial first slate?
当然是的
Absolutely.
我们的第一镜？
The first slate for our first shot.
我们会让我们的手指在上面流血吗?
Should we get our fingers open and bleed on it?
放一点点血?
A little blood-letting?
不 我们等下会保留这个的
No, we'll save that for later.
亲下这玩意吧
Kiss the slate.
这就是第一幕
It's the first slate.
上面有我的口红印
Marked by my lipstick.
迈克 来亲下 祝你好运
Mikey, kiss it, good luck.
- 我们要去哪？  - 他在咬着这东西了 祝福他
- There we go.  - Oh, he licked it. Bless him.
别吃下去 还要用的
Don't eat it. We're gonna need it.
这里是博克斯维尔 原来的布莱尔
This is Burkittsville, formerly Blair.
一个安静祥和的马里兰小镇
A small quiet Maryland town.
就像其他地方的小镇一样
Like a small, quiet town anywhere.
200年前这大约有20家人住在这
Some 20 families laid roots here over 200 years ago.
多数在这山丘附近
Many remain, either on this hill...
有的在小镇后面
...or in the town below.
异常多的孩子埋在这里
An unusually high number of children are buried here...
他们大多数在40年代去世的
...most of whom passed in the 1940's.
总之至今这里还没有人对我们说起那些
Yet no one here recalls anything unusual about this time, ...
那些不寻常的回忆
...not to us, anyway.
然而传说告诉了我们一个不寻常的故事
Yet legend tells A different story, ...
有个人一直在我们的周围
...whose evidence is all around us.
就像风化的岩石
Etched in stone.
我们已经拍摄了第一个场景 墓地
We have shot the first scene, the cemetery scene.
开拍了
The opening is shot.
我们在做关于女巫布莱尔的记录片
We're doing a documentary about the Blair Witch.
你听说过吗? 这是一个很老很老的故事了
- Have you heard of the Witch?  - That's an old, old story.
我记得
As I remember, ...
帕尔是一个年老的隐士
...Mr. Parr was an old hermit, ...
他住在高山上 他已经在那儿
...and he lived up on a mountain. He'd been there, ...
很长 很长时间了
...for a long, long, time.
你听说过女巫布莱尔吗?  -听说过几次
- You heard of the Blair Witch?  - Several times.
第一件事是什么?
What was the first incident?
我是从人们的谈论和邻居那儿听说的
I've heard stories about it from people and neighbors,
我也在电视的记录片上看过
I also saw a documentary on the television...
有关她在马里兰的传说
...about her and legends of Maryland, ...
我们的祖母为了让我早点睡觉 就把这个故事告诉我们
...my grandmother told us the story to make us go to bed early.
他们说你入夜还在这房子周围玩耍
They say if you stay up after dark or walk around the house...
女巫布莱尔就会抓住你
...the Blair witch will get you.
在1940年的秋天和冬天
In the fall or winter of 1940, ...
一些年幼的小孩开始失踪
...some young kids started disappearing.
没有人知道
Nobody knew...
为什么他们会失踪
...why they were disappearing.
我听过最吓人的事情是
- A kind of an omen, isn't it?  - The creepiest story about her...
大概是两个人出去打猎
...was that two men out hunting...
扎营在她经常出没的小屋附近
...camped near the cabin she's supposed to haunt...
不 不要
No. No.
然后就永远地消失了
...and they just disappeared forever.
我刚讲了个让人害怕的故事 但这不是真的
I'm just telling a scary story, but it's not true.
这不是真的
It's not true.
一天 老帕尔先生 走到市场里面
One day, old Mr. Parr came into the market...
说着 "我就要要完蛋了"
...and said "I'm finally finished".
他那样说是什么意思?
And what did he mean by that?
一开始没人知道
Nobody knew at first...
但最后警察
But the police finally...
走到他住的山上
went up the mountain...
发现有七个小孩的尸体在小屋里
...and found the bodies of seven kids in his house.
他会带两个小孩到地下室去
He would take the kids down to the basement in twos...
让一个面对着墙角
...and he'd make one face the corner...
然后把另一个杀掉
...and he'd kill the other one...
再把在墙角的那个也杀掉
...then he'd kill the one in the corner too.
他们就是那七个失踪的小孩
Those were the seven kids that were missing
他一次一个地把小孩带出森林
They brought the kids out of the woods one at a time...
这听上去很可怕 让全社会都震惊了
...it was terrible, it upset the whole community.
他说他不能接受眼前看到的他
He said he couldn't take the eyes watching him...
这就是为什么他让他们面对着墙角
...that's why he made them face the corner like that.
我一辈子都不相信
All my life I've believed...
什么女巫和鬼怪之类的
...in witches and ghosts and that kind of stuff
你不相信这里会有吗?
Do you believe there are some in this area?
是的 这很明确
Oh, definitely.
- 你不相信魔法之类吗?  - 不相信
- Do you believe in witchcraft?  - No.
- 你信教吗?  - 是的
- Are you religious?  - Yep.
好吧
Alrighty.
我想有什么事情 曾经在她身上发生
Creepy stuff, but I think something's happening with her.
你不认为她现在还活着吗?
And do you think she could still be up there now?
我不认为她还活着 真的不认为?
- I don't go up there.  - You don't?
我有足够的理由相信不要去那儿
I believe enough not to go.
他们说那片森林闹鬼什么的
They say the woods are haunted and stuff like that.
什么? 怎么个闹鬼法?
What? How are they haunted?
好吧 不是很多人说那儿闹鬼
Well there's not many people who say that it's haunted...
是一个老妇人 玛丽·布朗
...but there was this old woman, Mary Brown, who...
玛丽·布朗?
Mary Brown?
她有一些疯癫
Yeah, and she was kind of crazy.
她是什么样的人?
How was she seen by the community?
疯子
Crazy.
那里有个美国旗 那就是玛丽的房子了
There's the American flag, it's Mary's house.
我要把她说的说出去
I'm gonna bring her out.
你把最好的光线位找好 好?
You look for the best light, okay?
好
Okay.
这是玛丽家的大门
This is Mary's gate.
我还不知道怎样才能打开它
I'm not even sure how to open it.
一些有趣的事情会发生 一旦
And something interesting happened to you once...
你见过女巫布莱尔?
You met the Blair witch?
是的
Yes.
这是个真实的
That is really...
吓人的故事
...kind of a scary story.
一次可怕的遭遇
To make ends meet...
我爸爸和我
...my Dad and I
时常在小河钓鱼
...used to fish at Tappy's Creek.
在博克斯维尔
In Burkittsville.
我躺在树叶上
I was laying on the leaves...
盯着我的鱼竿 看着天空
...watching my pole, and looking at the sky...
突然我感觉有什么在靠近我
...and suddenly I felt something near me...
有一种恐惧的感觉
...an eerie feeling...
是一个女人
...It was a woman...
只能从手臂和手判断
...only on her arms and hands...
一切都
...and everything...
她有毛
...she had hair...
棕色的毛 几乎黑色的毛
...dark, almost black hair...
像马的毛一样
...like a horse...
就像一块皮毛 马的皮毛
...like a fur, horse fur.
当时在她的手臂上
Then on her arm...
有一块披肩
...she had a shawl...
她吓到你了
And she scared you, or threatened you?
她什么也没有说 她只是站在那儿
She didn't say anything, she just stared...
然后她打开它她的披肩
...and then she opened her shawl...
什么东西在里面?
What was under there?
她有头发 她的身体像马一样
She had hair on her body like a horse.
从头到脚全是毛?
Hairy from head to toe?
是的 她的腿
Yeah. And her legs...
- 她的脸是什么样的?
- How about her face?  - You could see she was a female.
她的样子看起来相当奇怪
She was just strange looking.
感谢上帝她不是在商业电影里
Thank God she's not in the film business.
她认为她是 她还说她是个芭蕾舞女
She thinks she is. She also says she's a ballerina.
行了
Get out.
她还说她是个历史学家
And she says she's a historian...
我听见了
I heard that.
她还说她是个能源局的科学家
...and that she's a scientist at the Department of Energy.
玛丽的口述资料很混乱
I fucked up on Mary with the depth of field.
你整理起来很费劲? 我们不是在欧洲
You measured it in meters? We're not in Europe.
这可恶的镜头都有记录
The fucking lens has meters on it.
还有我们的安排
It also has our system.
不 这里有仪表 看
Nah, it has meters. Look.
但这是个美国摄像机
But it's an American camera.
这些都是仪表
All those are meters.
这褐色的怎么样?
What about the brown ones?
你的脚
They're feet.
褐色的在那儿 对吗?
The brown ones are on there, right?
是的 但是这白色的更明显
Yeah, but the white ones are obvious.
你以前没用过这摄像机是吗? 是的以前有过一次
- Didn't you use this camera before?  - Yeah. Once before.
今天怎么样 小伙子?
How was today, guys?
学到很多 兄弟
I learned a lot, man.
有关 玛丽布朗的?
About Mary Brown?
不 我学到很多关于
No, I learned a lot about...
摄像机?
16 mill?
有关拍摄 拍摄记录片
...about shooting, just shooting documentaries.
我们很棒 干杯
- We kicked some ass today.  - Cheers.
今天不错
Very good day.
好极了
Excellent day.
第一天进行得非常顺利
Very good first day.
让我们检查下设备 待会儿我要打电话给我妈
Let's do an equipment check, after I call my mom.
我有一包零食和啤酒 我们不需要它出现在胶片上
- I got a bag of Utz and a beer.  - We don't need that on film.
所以我猜你最好把他们藏起来
So I guess you're covered then.
能否让它转起来让我检查一下?
Could you run it a little to check it's okay?
当然可以
Sure.
我只想检查看它是否能读取 以便拍摄
I just want to check it's loaded properly so we can shoot...
好 很好 很好
Okay, that's good, that's good.
很好 谢谢
That's good, thank you.
放松下 因为我们的明天还长着呢
Let's relax, because we've got a long day tomorrow.
今天很轻松
Today's been easy.
我们将要徒步很长时间 带很多重家伙
We're gonna have to do a lot of hiking, carry a lot of weight.
我们在准备着
We're preparing.
住口 让我好好拍 求你了
Shut up, smart-ass. Pour me a shot, please.
我很怪诞 你不是你是导演嘛
- I'm freaking out.  - You can't, you're the director.
我现在他妈的必须做这个了 好? 我们还有什么别的么?
I fucking have to do this now, okay? Do we have any weed?
要开始了
Here I go.
喝! 喝
Drink! Drink!
我他妈讨厌苏格兰人
I hate fucking scotch.
这是我朋友 乔什
There's my friend Josh.
还好吗?
How are you?
我受伤了'
I'm hurtin'.
我还没准备好那些东西
I'm not ready for that thing yet.
我知道你不喜欢这个
I know you don't like it.
Hello 欢迎来到第二天
Hello. Welcome to day two.
顺着这条路
The trail is along here.
这应该很漂亮
It should be pretty obvious.
你这家伙听说过女巫布莱尔吗?
You guys heard of the Blair witch?
我听过这神话 我不相信
I heard the myth. I don't really believe much in it.
神话?
The myth?
这是我自己的想法
That's all I think it is.
你说什么 先生?
What'd you say, sir?
我说蠢货是从来不聪明 闭嘴
- I said damn fool kids never learn.  - Shut up.
蠢货从来不聪明?
Damn fool kids never learn?
这就是我想说的
That's what I said.
为什么这样说?
Why do you say that?
首先 我可以得到你的许可
First of all, can I have your permission...
使用你的肖像在这部记录片上吗?
...to use your image on a video documentary?
我不介意 但
I don't care about that, but...
你只需回答是或不是先生
You have to say yes or no, sir,
看这 对不起
- Watch it.  - I'm sorry.
好的 没问题 好
Yeah, sure, okay.
一些女孩子在19世纪晚期
Some girl, in the late 1800's...
我相信她的名字是罗宾
...Robin Weaver, I believe her name was, ...
我想大概是在森林里走失了
...supposedly wandered off into the woods.
不是 "我想" 确实是走丢了
No "supposedly" about it. She wandered off!
好吧 那就是走丢了 丢了
- Okay, wandered off.  - And got lost.
她迷路了
She got lost.
并非 "我想"
Wasn't no "supposedly".
三天后
Three days later...
她重新出现在她祖母家的门口
...she appears back on her grandmother's porch.
每个人都感到迷惑不解
And everybody's mystified.
她口里模糊的在说些什么 她的故事
- She was babbling something...  - Her story.
不清不楚的说有关于
Babbling something about...
一个漂浮在地面上的女人
...an old woman whose feet never touched the ground.
我看见 小溪上的那棵树
I saw... just by that tree up the creek...
离我们大概有100码
...about a hundred yards,
我看见一团白雾状的东西 我也说不清楚是什么
I saw a white misty thing. Can't tell you what it was.
就像是灰白色的蒸汽在树上升起来吗
Like grey vapor rising out of the trees.
是在水面上升起
Right out of the water.
在水面上升起?
Right out of the water?
升到树顶上 就消失不见了
Up the side of the trees, Then it disappeared.
你喝醉了吧
You're full of it.
没有 我那天一点酒都没有喝
I'm not. And I wasn't drinking that day, either.
你确定没有？
Sure you weren't.
这和科菲岩有什么关系吗?
How is that related to the story of Coffin Rock?
和科菲岩很密切
It all ties in to the story of Coffin Rock.
怎么讲?
How's that?
周围没有人
Anybody round here...
知道这些年来有个神秘的老女 人在这出没
...knows that the old woman has haunted this area for years.
简直是胡说
That's bullshit.
这片森林太浓密了
These woods are thick.
你兴奋吗?
You excited?
你不也是吗
You got it.
我希望他不要拍出一堆狗屎来
I hope he's not shooting a whole shitload of stock.
我帮不上什么忙 但我会忠实的记录 发生的一切的
I could help, but I'd rather record.
好
Okay.
带上包 准备出发
Packs on, we're ready to go.
我们真的要上到那小屋子里吗?
We gotta go up to the shack?
是的
Yeah.
天啊 这包真重
My God, this is a very heavy pack.
到 科菲岩去
Off to Coffin Rock.
我很清楚我们在哪
I know exactly where we are now.
迈克 给我摄像机
Mikey, give me the video camera.
我希望她能过去 伙计们
I wanna get her going across, man.
我看到你的屁股很脏
I see a dirty behind.
跳得不错
Good jump.
谢谢
Thank you.
是那儿了 看见了吗?
There it is. See?
那儿就是 科菲岩
That's Coffin Rock.
"他们走进森林是寻找死者
"They went into the woods ready to find death...
但他们找到了一个恐怖的
...but what they found was inhumane...
叫科菲岩的地方
...at the site called Coffin Rock.
在这块岩石之上
...up on the rock, the torture...
明显可以看出有五个勇敢男人
...suffered by these five brave men was obvious...
他们被绑着 一个人的手绑在另一个人的脚上
...they were tied up, one man's hands tied to the next man's feet...
构成一个坚固的整体
...forming a solid human structure...
那些血迹表明发生了某些事
...blood indicated that it had happened...
当时他们还活着并且有反抗
...while they were alive and resisting...
他们的内脏已经被撕破
...their intestines had been crudely torn out...
他们的脸上都写着一些难以解释的文字
...and on each of their faces there was indecipherable writing...
一直深入到肉里面
...cut into their flesh with precision...
他们震惊地看这眼前发生的一切
...the men, shocked by what had happened...
准备报告警察
...went to find the sheriff...
他们没有什么计划 也没有去碰那些尸体
...without sketching the writing or touching the bodies...
等他们返回时见秃鹰在岩石上
...they returned to see vultures at the rock.
但那些尸体也不知道被谁移走了
But the bodies had been removed by persons unknown...
死亡的臭气依然浓重
...the stench of death was still thick...
尸体被搬走大概有一小时了
...but the bodies had been taken in a matter of hours..."
这就是发生在科菲岩的事
That happened here at Coffin Rock.
快走吧 我们还要赶去扎营 现在是4:52
Let's rush, because I want to camp, and it's 4:52.
有点晚了 天快要黑了
It's late. We're gonna be losing light soon.
我不会让我在镜头里消失的
But I can use the shot without me in it...
因为我还要讲述整件事的经过
...because I recorded sound while reading the whole thing, ...
我能确定我能剪辑好这些
...so I'm sure I can edit it together somehow.
下雨了
It's starting to rain.
这玩意是你租来的?
Did you rent this thing?
是的 我没有能供三个人住的帐篷
Yeah. I don't have a tent for three people.
我还奇怪
Just wondering...
我以前还没和两个男人一起露过营呢
I don't usually travel with two men.
雨水正流进来 我们还可以升火吗？
It is pouring with rain. Can't even light a fire.
让我们看看这棍子是干什么的
Show us what the stick is for.
看 我们有我们特有的柱子
Look. We've got our very own leaning post.
如果晚上这里的味道太难闻
If it smells of farts too much in the night...
好的 我不会在帐篷里吸烟的
Okay, so I can't have a cigarette in the tent, ...
但是他可以吗?
...but he can fart as much as he wants?
不 别让他这么做
No, I never gave Mike a fart allowance.
昨晚你听见了什么声响没有?
You heard noises last night?
是的 问题是 我睡得像块木头
- I did.  - Problem is, I sleep like a log.
分别有两种声音
There were two separate noises...
从两个地方发出来
...coming from two areas over here...
一个像鸟叫
...one of them could have been an owl...
另一个就咯咯叫
...but the other was a cackling.
决不是的
No way.
是咯咯叫 伙计
It was a cackling, man.
如果是咯咯叫 我TM就是狗屎
If I heard a cackling, I would've shit myself.
昨天我们是从哪开始的?
Where did we start yesterday?
不在地图上
Off the map.
我知道我们从哪出发的 这有些乱 但今天
I knew where we were going. There was some confusion, but today...
等下再说一遍
Wait, ... say that again.
我说我知道我们从哪出发的
I said I knew where we were going.
等下这是什么狗屁解释啊?
Wait, ... was that a full of shit statement?
不 才不是呢
No, it wasn't.
这还不是胡说? 我知道我们从哪出发的
- So that wasn't bullshit?  - I knew where we were going.
你让我们迷路了 伙计
You got us lost, man.
就一会儿而已
For a very short period of time.
今天别再让我迷路了
Just don't get us lost today.
好的 我是认真的
Yeah, seriously.
不 这些地方都是有注明的
No. These places are very well documented.
你为我们的这不记录片感到高兴吗?
You happy with the documentary?
是的 当然
Yes, I am.
我对我们的小迈克感到惊喜
I'm very pleasantly surprised by our little Mikey.
“我们的小迈克?”
"Our Little Mikey?"
我们的小迈克
Our Little Mikey...
一个很英勇的小伙子
...a very spirited young man.
你对女巫有什么想法? 你认为她存在吗?
What do you think about the witch? You think she exists?
不知道
I don't know.
海瑟 我真希望能找到她的踪迹
Heather, I really hope you find us a trail.
我们会在这山上找到的 别担心
There's a trail up on this hill. Don't worry.
我们喜欢抄捷径 对吗?
We like shortcuts, don't we?
我只喜欢平的捷径
We like level shortcuts.
不是山上的这种
Not mountain shortcuts.
这是我们第一次看见迈克的胸
It's the first time we've seen Mike's chest.
真是不上镜啊
It's really hard to film on video.
他胸上的毛很有意思
He has really sporadic hair patterns on his chest.
就像符号似的
Like symbols.
一块空白一块毛
It's like blank... hairy...
...blank... hairy.
你想看我的屁股
You should see my ass.
看 这里是乌拉圭
Look, here's fucking Uruguay.
还有这是巴拉圭 是的
- And there's Paraguay.  - Yeah.
我想我看见了玻利维亚
I think I see Bolivia.
这只老鼠怎么死的? 巫术?
What killed this mouse? Witchcraft?
还是和上帝的较量的结果?
How 'bout God?
是女巫布莱尔?
Is that the Blair Witch?
不 我认为是海瑟在小便
No. I think it's Heather, taking a piss.
知道吗 我们得走了
You know, I really have to go.
走吧
Ohhh... go!
接近墓地的样子了 那只…
We're near the cemetery trail. It should only be...
什么? 我吗?
- What?  - Says who?
我说的 当然
Says me, of course.
我们到那儿大概要90分钟
We should be there in about ninety minutes.
你这家伙一点都不在意吗
You guys cool with that?
什么?
What?
90分钟?
Ninety minutes?
只要你知道怎么走 当然
- If you know where we're going.  - Sure.
乔什 现在想看看地图
Josh wants to look at the map now.
尽管我知道怎么走
Though I know where we're going.
如果你知道怎么走 我们就
If you'd known where we were, we wouldn't be...
他妈不会在森林的中央啦
We're in the middle of the fucking woods.
你怎么知道的? 因为这些看上去就像是
- How could you possibly know?  - Because some is off trail.
什么 有人告诉你那后面有个墓地吗?
What, somebody told you there's a cemetery back there?
如果我们迷路了 你就承认吧 因为
If we're lost, admit that, because...
我知道我们迷路了
...I know we're not lost.
昨天你也是这样 今天可是第二次了
You knew that yesterday, too, and twice again today.
瞎说 我们今天没走丢
Bullshit! We have not been lost today.
从来没有
Not once.
好 我们现在在哪？
Okay, this is where we were.
你说那儿只有两英里
You said that it was two miles away.
现在两个小时过去了 三个小时过去了
Then it's two hours away, three hours away...
好 冷静 也许四个小时都过去了
- Okay, just chill!  - Maybe it's four hours away.
你都同意了这个计划的 我只同意了走出去这个计划
- You agreed to do this project.  - I agreed to a scouted-out project.
而不是围这这森林打转 我告诉你
- Not to wander round the woods.  - I told you that...
走出去不是那么容易的
...getting to the locations wasn't gonna be easy.
迈克 迈克 好了 伙计们!
Mike, Mike... Okay, guys!
请不要那么冲动
Please, you're being a smart-ass.
我们正在看地图
We're looking at the map...
我们会找到出路的
...we'll find this the best we can.
这就是我们所在的地方 我们或多或少走过这条路
This is where we were. We're going more or less this way.
好 你说什么? 接下来怎么做?
Okay, what do you say? Where do you think we're going?
说实话吧
To tell you the truth...
我也不想这样 这没用
...this is Greek to me. It's useless.
很正确
Exactly.
那么我相信你
So I'm putting my trust in you...
你知道我们在哪
...that you know where it is.
很好
Good.
但我还是必须告诉你 我不能完全信任你
Though I gotta tell you, I don't fully trust you...
并且我
...and I...
什么?
What?
我不知道为什么你录下所有谈话 兄弟
I don't know why you tape every conversation, man.
无语了 我们是在做记录片啊！
Well, we're making a documentary.
不是关于我们迷路的 是关于女巫的
Not about us getting lost, it's about a witch!
我有摄像机
I have a camera.
我们会回忆起这些和我们的笑声 相信我吧
We'll all look back on this and laugh, believe me.
有台阶 有台阶
Baby steps, man, baby steps.
深呼吸 别往下看 不 你必须往下看
Just breathe and don't look down. No, you gotta look down.
你不会是想爬过去吧?
Are you gonna have to crawl?
我想是的
I'm gonna crawl.
酷毙了
Cool.
想像下 他妈的就快到墓地了会有多爽
Think how cool the fucking cemetery is gonna be.
想像下这在胶片上会多有趣
Think of the joy of being in a really good film.
好 闭嘴
Okay, shut the fuck up.
好 我不说了
Okay, I'm quiet.
妈的 我该怎么办?
Shit. How am I gonna do this?
好了吗 迈克?
Okay... Mikey?
嗯
Yeah.
哥们 不要把录音带放在你的腰上走过来
Dude, don't come across with the DAT on your belly.
不会的 兄弟
No way, man.
没机会了
There's no chance.
我该怎么过去?
How do we get it across?
真他妈难办
It's really fucking hard.
怎么过去呢?
How we gonna get it across?
这些小青苔的早晨过得可真舒服 真他妈滑啊
The moss this morning was easy. This stuff's slippery as shit.
好吧 怎么把录像带弄过来?
Well, how do we get the DAT across?
不知道 让我先把包放下
I don't know. Let me put my pack down...
我会回去拿的 兄弟
I'll just go back and forth, man.
你能办到吗?
Can you do it that way?
只有这件事我可以
It's the only thing I can do.
好 就那样干吧
Okay, we'll do it like that.
上帝
Oh, Christ!
什么掉下去了?
Oh, what'd you drop?
没什么 这树干掉了一块
Nothing. The tree just broke.
他妈的
Oh, fuck.
我们现在很接近了
We're very, very close now.
伙计们 兴奋吗?
You guys excited?
好
Okay.
这是什么?
What's this?
这是什么? 哥们
What's this? Dude, guys.
还记得那天 玛丽 布朗 说了些什么吗?
Remember what Mary Brown said the other day?
她告诉我们关于布莱尔的故事?
What story from the Bible was she telling us?
妈的 我没有听 我以为她疯了呢
Fuck, I wasn't listening, I thought she was crazy.
这是以扫[圣经] 用石头堆起来的东西
It was Esau, something about a pile of rocks.
她说过她的石头兄弟
She was talking about her rocks, man.
好吧 说什么了?
Well, what about the rocks?
还有人记得吗?
Anybody remember?
让生活充满活力
To live your life.
这看起来像印地安人的墓地 伙计
Looks like an Indian burial ground, man.
我不知道这些加起来有多少 三
I don't know if this counts, three...
四
...four...
五
...five...
六
...six...
七
...seven.
多年前女巫
Years ago witches were roasted...
被烤得像维也纳香肠一样
...just like my Vienna sausage.
火焰像恶魔一样鞭打着你 乔什
Flames are licking you like the Devil, Josh.
Sit back and hear a tale, a tale of a fateful trip...
...that started on this desert isle...
...aboard this tiny ship...
但船上有位好船长
Yeah, but this ship has a good captain...
而不是穿着兰色上衣的酒鬼
...not a beer-guzzling guy in a blue shirt.
他不是酒鬼
He wasn't beer-guzzling.
那岛上没有啤酒 兄弟
They had no beer on the island, man.
如果那有酒 他们就会有个大屁股
If they had beer, they'd have had big-ass orgies.
你就像是船长 迈克就是你的情人
You're like the Captain, and Mike's your Gilligan.
不 谢谢 很好
- No offense.  - That's all right.
我是说这是一种称赞
It was a compliment...
情人是个小伙子
...Gilligan was a funny guy...
尽管船长很肥
...the Captain was fat, though.
好吧 让我们叫声船长吧
Well okay, let's call it a thin Captain.
不是船长
It's not Captain...
是船长
It's the Skipper.
不再是了
No more Captain.
我们要再回到那些石块那儿去
Here we are back at the rock again...
那个墓地
...the cemetery deal.
我只想小心些不要被拍到镜头里
I just wanna be careful not to get in the shot.
像我说的
It certainly is odd.
别告诉我是你打翻了它们
Please tell me you didn't just knock that over.
我没打翻它们
I didn't just knock that over.
这可不妙 把它放回去吧
That's not very nice. Let me put it back.
你要小心些
You can't be too careful.
你认为呢?
What'd you think?
我的想法也差不多 太暗了
It was the same, only darker.
是的 差不多了
Yeah, pretty much.
好的 装到带子里吧
All right. Bag it up.
有人吗?
Hello?
妈的 没有光
Shit, no light.
睡觉去吧
We were sleeping.
你想这样?
Do you want this?
把它放在帐篷门口好了
Put it by the tent door.
听
Listen.
有人吗?
Hello?
有人吗
Hello!
周围都是声音 真怪异
It's all around us. Fucking weird.
迈克尔 你跟下来了吗?
Michael, aren't you coming down?
我没有下来
I ain't going down there.
为什么不?
Why not?
因为我什么也没听见 你被吓怕了吧
- Because I don't hear shit.  - You're fucking scared.
因为我什么也没听见!
Because I don't hear anything!
你不要否认听见了什么
You cannot deny hearing it.
快出来 快
Get your ass out! Come on!
又是风又是雨的伙计
This rain fucking blows, man.
我知道 雨下得很大
I know. It's raining heavily.
感谢我妈在我生日的时候送了我副雨具
Thanks mom for giving me rain gear for my birthday.
上帝保佑她
God bless her.
你怎么看昨晚的事?
What do you think it was last night?
亲身感受?
Personally?
是的
Yeah.
一定他妈的有人搞鬼
Someone fucking with your head.
没人知道我们在这
But nobody knows we're here.
是的 但你看过《生死狂澜》吗?
Yeah, but... you ever see "Deliverance"?
好 不管那是什么 我只想
Well, whatever it was, I just wanted to...
你真是吓坏了 你让我突然想退出
You were freaking out. You bugged me out.
我是有些吓坏了 我夜里突然醒来又睡下
I was. I woke up suddenly and shit's going down...
我脑海里想的是 “我想这全是
...and all I can think is "I want it all...
我想全是声音
I want it on sound, I want it on sixteen.
如果我们看见什么东西 我想拍下来”
If we see anything, I want it on sixteen."
那些声音就像是很多人在周围跑
Sounded to me like a lot of people running around...
也许他们是本地人或是其他地方的
...maybe they were locals or whatever.
我不知道他们为何像在地狱里般狂奔
I don't know what the hell they wanted.
我们深陷在森林里 如果有人想和我们捣乱
We're deep in the woods, and if people want to mess with us...
那我想他们一定有病
...then there's something wrong with them...
我不打算进森林了
...and I'm not gonna get into that.
如果不是人呢?
And if it wasn't people?
那我也不会进去的
Well, I'm not gonna get into that, either!
妈的 伙计们
Fuck, man...
今天真是漫长
... it's been a very long day...
潮湿 漫长的一天啊
...a very wet, very long day.
现在没人愿意和我说话
Nobody's speaking to me right now.
哥们 我不记得这个了
Dude, I don't remember any of this.
记得什么?
What?
我不记得从车里到这的路了
I don't remember any of this coming from the car.
我们必须走别的路回去
We have to go a different route to get back...
因为我们在绕圈
...because we went around in a curve.
两个多小时了 小伙子们
Two more hours max, guys.
如果我们走的是捷径 那为什么我们回去要走不同的路线?
If we came by a short cut, why are we going back a different way?
因为我们必须要绕道走
Because we have to go round...
我们要把更多精力放在我们的两个拍摄地上
It was the most direct way to hit our two locations.
这是回到车上最快的路
And this is the quickest way back to the car.
坦白说这是真的吗?
Seriously?
是的 我是认真的
Yes. Seriously.
你确定知道我们该怎么走吗? 是的 我们继续前进吧
- You know exactly what's going on?  - Yes. Let's just keep going.
好的
All right.
五分钟看一次地图
Five minutes and we do a map check.
好的
All right.
我们查看下地图 我们还在这路上
We just did a map check, and we're still on track.
这可不是我说的
That's not what I said.
我们走对了 来吧 继续前进
We're all right. Come on, just keep going.
罗盘指示
Well the compass says...
我们得直走 那条路
...we go straight ahead, that way.
我们不知道位置了
We're in the middle of nowhere.
我们都两天不知道位置了
We've been in the middle of nowhere for two days.
就像那车
Just like the car.
看这 兄弟! 这什么也不是
Look at this shit, man! This is nothing.
继续走 好吗?
Let's just keep going, all right?
我想我们该扎营了
I think we should camp.
从这他妈的鬼地方出去
Get the fuck out of here!
为什么? 因为我们不知道我们在哪?
Why? 'Cause you don't know where we are?
不 因为我们离那辆车只有一小步
No, because we're still A little way from the car...
并且天马上要暗下来了
...and it's gonna be dark soon.
- 看 我不能确信  - 我们不能扎营
- Look, I'm not sure...  - We don't camp. Stop the camera...
回去吧
...and get us home.
关上这他妈的摄像机 把地图给我
Turn the camera off and give me the fucking map.
关上让我们回家吧
Turn it off and get us home.
不 我正在拍着 我想抓住机会
No, I'm filming. I want to mark this occasion.
给我地图
Give me the map.
地图在我包里 稍等会
The map is in my pocket. Wait a second.
该死的
God damn!
只要我们团结起来 一切都会好的
If we keep our heads together, we'll be just fine.
扯他妈的淡
Fucking bullshit!
迈克 冷静
Mike, chill.
放松些 迈克
Just relax, Mike.
别告诉我什么鬼放松些
Don't fucking tell me to relax!
在这站会儿 查看下地图
Let's just sit down, and check the map...
好的 就这样做
Yes. Let's do that, please.
不高兴了?
Are you happy?
很不爽 是的
I'm not happy, no.
车离这不远了 但我们在天黑前是找不到的
But the car isn't far. But we can't find it in the dark.
你确信?
Are you absolutely sure?
是的 很抱歉 我们明天仍旧可以把录像带带回去
Yes. I'm so sorry. We can still get the DAT back tomorrow.
我们必须
We have to...
我们会准时回去的
We will get the DAT back on time.
和这些胶片
And the camera.
我们明天会把它们带回去的
We'll get it all back tomorrow.
我明天九点要开始工作了
I start work tomorrow at nine.
我知道
I know.
很好去睡觉吧
It's fine. Let's go to sleep.
我们扎营 好?
Let's just fucking camp, okay?
我想要帐篷里的带子
I wanna tape it from inside the tent.
不管是什么 那声音听起来和昨晚一样
Whatever it is, it sounds the same as last night.
我的鞋呢? 我靠 太冷了
Where's my boots? Fuck, it's cold...
有人吗?
Hello?
靠 真他妈的冷啊
Shit, it's fucking freezing...
那儿
...there.
什么?
What?
我听见什么了
I hear it.
我什么也听不见
I don't hear shit.
你听见了吗?
You hear that?
妈的
Shit...
有人吗?
Hello?
我想那只是鹿而已
I think it's just a deer.
我猜不会是鹿 就是鹿
- Could be deer, I guess.  - It's just a deer.
我不认为 兄弟
I don't think so, man.
那声音像昨晚的一样 在我们的周围都是
Sounds just like last night. It's all around us.
那只是鹿而已
It's gotta be just a deer.
是鹿 兄弟
It was a deer, man.
这和昨晚的不一样
It wasn't like last night.
你说什么?
You say something?
是的 快听 用带子把它录下来 安静
Yes! Fucking listen! Let's get it on DAT... be quiet...
好 它开着
Okay, it's on.
天哪 那到底是什么?
Jesus Christ! What the fuck was that?
别自己吓自己了
It's not scared by our yelling.
那声音像脚步声
Sounds like footsteps.
我知道 那他妈的是个人
I know! It's a fucking person!
摄像机上什么也看不见 只能用带子录下来 对不?
I don't see shit on video. We'll just use DAT, right?
我们在户外
But I'm staying out.
你和我一起
You stay out here with me.
是的 是的
I am. I am.
现在几点了? 什么时候才到早上啊?
What time is it? Anywhere near morning?
我看下表先
Let me see...
告诉我是五点了或是别的时间
Tell me it's five O'clock or something.
三点
Three.
妈的
Fuck!
扯淡 真他妈疯了
Bullshit. This is fucking crazy.
对不起 迈克 我们应该呆在家的
I'm sorry, Mike. We should be home already.
现在我们在这里
This has got nothing to do...
什么也不能做
...with what we're here for.
真是胡言乱语
This is just it's bullshit.
今早起来 不久前
Woke up this morning, two seconds ago...
我们的帐篷外有些小石堆
...and there are piles of rocks outside our tent.
事实上是有三个
There are three, actually.
你确定昨天晚上没有?
Are you positive those weren't there last night?
肯定没有
I am fucking positive they weren't here!
我们怎么可能那么巧扎营
How could we have just camped...
在这些石头堆之间?
...between three piles of rocks just by coincidence?
你不觉得这很奇怪吗?
You don't think this is strange?
太不可思议了 但我真的不在意
It is fucking weird, but I really don't care...
因为我只想回到那该死的车上
...because all I want to do is get to the goddam car.
不管这是哪 伙计 现在
Whatever it is, man, right now...
我们必须回到车上去
...we have to get back to the car.
很显然他们不喜欢我们待在这里 所以想让我们滚出去
They obviously don't want us Here, so let's get out.
我们得把带子拿回去
We have to get the DAT back.
我也这样想 好吧 我们走
- That's what I mean.  - Okay, let's go.
带上这些赶紧走人吧！
Let's pack our shit up and just walk.
可以走了吗?
Can we just walk?
是的 离开这
Yes, we're out of here.
好 太好了
Okay, cool.
一切都发生在我们要走的时候
But we're leaving just when it's all happening.
把摄像机放下 来收拾帐篷吧
Put the fucking camera down. Let's pack up the tent.
快走出这里吧 好的 坚持会
- Let's get out of the woods.  - Okay, hang on.
快
Come on!
不 我没有害怕 我只是又累又饿
No, I'm not scared! I'm just tired and hungry...
我快要完蛋了 兄弟
I'm just fucking done, man.
好吧
All right.
地图在你那儿?
Did you take it?
没有 我没拿那鬼地图
No, I didn't take the fucking map.
我没有和你开玩笑
I'm not playing head games.
是你在开玩笑
You're the one playing head games.
而不是我
But I'm not.
我们得走了 我是认真的 地图不在我这
I don't have it. We have to go. I'm serious, I don't have it.
你他妈是认真的?
Are you fucking serious?
我他妈是认真的 地图不在我这
Fucking serious. I don't have it.
海瑟 这一点也不好玩 伙计
Heather, that is not so cool, man.
我知道这不好玩
I know it's not cool!
你对这东西
It's the fucking least responsible thing...
一点也不负责 兄弟
...you could have done, man.
我知道
I know that.
地图没了?
You really don't have it?
你们中一定有个人拿了
One of you must have the map.
不 我没有地图 我们昨天看完就
No, I don't have the map. We gave it back to you...
把地图给了你了
...after map check yesterday.
我一直把它放在同一个地方
I always keep it in the same place...
如果不是在那儿 那就是你们拿了
...and if it's not there, one of you must have it.
我他妈才没有那该死的地图 兄弟
I did not get the goddam map out of your fucking pants, man.
好吧 我没有
Well, I don't have it!
想想 我为什么要拿它?
Look, why would I take it?
我只想从这里出去
I just wanna get out of here, man.
我也是
Me too.
那我们走吧
Let's go!
不 你只想留在这拍片 到处看
No, you wanna stay and film rocks, look around...
我们走
Let's go!
你又想拍这又想拍那的 走哪边啊?
...you wanna film this and that... Which way?
这边
That way.
我们在森林的中间
We're in the middle of the woods!
我们哪儿也去不了
We can walk any way!
这边 因为我们整天都在走这条路
This way! Because we've been going this way all day.
我们走这边 我们得找些东西
We're going this way! We gotta find something!
我已经把地图还给你了
I gave you back the map!
我给了你
I gave you the map.
我已经把地图还给你了
I gave you back the map!
走吧 尽快走吧
- Let's just go.  - We can move as fast as we want...
漫无目的 我们不知道要走去哪
...but there's no point if we have no idea where we're going.
我们可以顺这小溪走 迈克看起来喜欢那样
We're following the creek. Mike seems happy with that.
停下来干什么?
Would you guys stop it?
我们注定完了
We are fucked, we are done...
我们死定了
...we are dead, we are fucked.
我要留在这 如果你遇到人
I'm staying here. When you find someone...
告诉他们我和这些树藤躺在树下
...tell them I'm under the tree with the vine.
所有的责备都
All blame aside...
我们完蛋了
...this is really fucked up.
我知道
I know.
我们需要在一起工作
We really need to work together.
我了解 对对
- I realize that.  - Exactly. Exactly.
我们必须接受相机和数据没了的现实
So we accept the fact that my camera's not gonna be back...or your DAT.
现在什么也不要埋怨了
No blame from now on about that shit.
你瞧 说真的
Look, seriously...
这个地方也不是很大
...this area's not that fucking big.
对 目前在美国很难走丢
Exactly. It's very hard to get lost in America these days...
一直走丢就更难了
...and even harder to stay lost.
什么?
What?
好吧 我们在做一个迷路的工作
Well, we're doin' a pretty good job of being lost.
你们今天回不去 我今天也回不去
If you're not home today, and I'm not home today...
人们就会注意到
...people are gonna notice...
我女朋友更会注意到
...My girlfriend's definitely gonna notice...
她会注意我没打电话给她
...and she'll notice that I haven't called.
我没回去 也没给她打电话
...that I didn't get back and I didn't call...
如果我们今晚没找到路
...so if by tonight we haven't found shit...
他们就会来找我们
...someone's gonna be looking for us.
噢 不
Oh, no!
别从这里下 走别的路
Not down here, go another way...
他妈的都湿了
...I just got my whole shit wet.
妈的好吧 试试别的路吧
Shit. Well, let's try it this way.
不 不是这
No, not this way...
那里会好些
...better try the other way.
如果我们没带这些包会轻松些 我不是想笑
- If we didn't have these packs...  - I don't mean to laugh...
你的脚都湿了
Your feet are wet!
迈克尔在笑话你?
Is Michael laughing?
闭嘴 快过来
Shut up and cross the stream.
他在笑你
He's laughing...
这是我第一次见你笑
...that's the first time you've laughed in days.
我很高兴你不是愁眉苦脸的
I'm happy you find it amusing...
那样我休息时会很不舒服的
...that I'll be uncomfortable for the rest of the day.
哥们 不会不舒服很久的
Dude, uncomfort does not even...
继续走 好吗?
Can we keep going, please?
不 冷静
No, we're gonna chill out!
你不是想上车的吗?
- Didn't you want to get to the car?  - Oh boy!!
好 快快走吧
Okay, come on... let's get up here.
靠 妈的
Oh shit.
你不认为地图在我身上吗?
You weren't lying to me about the map, were you?
你看上去很可笑
'Cause to me it seems like you're having a little too much fun.
噢 海瑟 我们快要发疯了
- Oh, Heather...  - We're going a little stir crazy.
海瑟如果你让我在这里发火
Heather! If you make me yell at this point...
别让我对你 兄弟
...don't make me yell at you, man.
说真的 如果地图在你那儿 我只想 知道地图在你那儿
Seriously, if you got the map, I just wanna know you have it!
那会让我很高兴 只要知道地图在你那儿
That would make me happy, just to know you have it.
如果我知道在你那儿 我看到它 我会 觉得好过些
If I knew that, and I could see it, I'd feel much better.
我们只是设法让你镇定些
We're just trying to be cool with you.
所以你们就笑我的鞋湿了
So I get laughed at 'cause my shoes got wet.
真够搞笑的
It's fucking hilarious.
我们的都湿了
All our shoes are wet...
我们笑我们的遭遇
...we were laughing at the situation.
好的
Fine.
真他妈又累又饿
We're fucking hungry and fucking tired...
还有什么可做的吗? 你知道吗?
- ...what the hell else can we do?  - You know what?
不好意思 你们受骗了
I'm sorry, it's fucked up...
昨天是我把地图踢到小溪里了
...but I kicked that map into the creek yesterday.
那玩意没用 我就把它踢到小溪里了
It was useless and I kicked it into the creek!
我他妈的希望他是在开玩笑
I fucking hope he's kidding.
迈克?
Mike?
我真他妈的希望他是在开玩笑
I really fucking hope he's kidding.
迈克 你是在开玩笑吧?
Mike, are you fucking kidding?
抱歉 兄弟 很抱歉
I'm sorry, man. I'm sorry.
你是和我开玩笑 你一定是在和我 开玩笑
You're kidding me. You have gotta be fucking kidding me!
你以为这是儿戏吗? 滚开
- You think it's a game?  - Get off me!
你他妈的是在干嘛? 你疯了吗?
What the fuck? Are you out of your mind?
不 不是 地图什么用也没有
No, I'm not. That map wasn't doing shit!
对你是这样 但我知道它说什么
Not for you, but I knew what the fuck the map said!!
抱歉
I'm sorry!
你这个混蛋
You're a fucking asshole!
对不起
I'm sorry.
你这个混蛋
You're a fucking asshole!
那地图没有用
That map was useless!
如果我们有什么事 那这都是你的错
If we get hurt or die here, it's your fucking fault!
你明白吗?
You understand?
怎么有你这样的混蛋?
How could you be such an asshole?
你到底在想什么? 你是来搞事的
- What were you thinking?  - You are fucking me up here!
我不是 那地图没用
I am not! That map was useless!
对你才没用
It was useless to you!
好吧
Okay...
我这样不能带你出去 兄弟
I didn't bring you out here for this, man.
我对这地图感到抱歉 兄弟 我还能说什么呢?
Sorry about the map, man. What can I say?
这地图根本没用 不用说抱歉
- The map wasn't doing shit.  - Just don't say sorry.
这地图对你没什么价值
It wasn't worth shit to you.
我知道我们在哪
I knew exactly where we were!
听好 昨天我问你我们在哪条河上
Listen! Yesterday I asked you what fucking river we were on...
少说两句吧
Shut up or else.
关上这该死的摄像机吧
Turn the fucking camera off!
给我指南针
Give me the compass...
你已经出卖了我们
...you have betrayed us...
找不到路了 把指南针给我
...way fucking beyond. Give me the compass.
你让我们出不去了
So have you for not getting us out of the woods.
好的 谢谢
Yeah, thanks.
我能拿着这指南针吗?
Can I have the fucking compass?
不 这是我买的 如果你想要
No. I bought the compass. If you wanted one...
就自己去买
...you should've bought your own.
你他妈和他都把我搞乱了
You and he both fucked us up.
为什么你不承认
Why can't you admit that...
你一开始就把我们搞迷糊了 让我们向南走
- ...you fucked up from the start.  - Let's just walk south.
因为我没有
Because I haven't!
我们为什么停下来?
Why are we stopped?
别问了
Just don't.
我只是问我们为什么停下来
I'm just asking Why we stopped.
我们不是向南?
Weren't we going south?
我们看上去对原来的计划很满意
We all seemed very Happy with that.
为什么不继续下去?
Why don't we carry on like that?
什么?
What?
这里有各种各样的素材
There's all sorts of Stuff down here!
什么样的?
What kind of stuff?
巫术
Voodoo shit!
什么?
What?
这里挂得到处都是 决不
- Hanging all over the place!  - No way...
这都是
It's all over.
神秘的样子
Holy shit...
快 我需要更多光线
Come up quick! I need the CP!
这什么样子的都有 伙计
There's all sorts Here, man!
这太疯狂了
This is fucking crazy shit.
我必须记录下来
Please, I gotta film this!
拿着摄像机
Take the fucking camera.
这他妈的是什么?
What the fuck is this?
不知道
I have no idea.
主啊 这真恶心
Jesus Christ, that's fucking creepy.
这不会是乡下人做的 他们没有这样的创造力
This is no redneck. No redneck is this creative.
我们现在可以继续前进了吗?
Can we go now?
好的 走吧
Yeah, please.
好 我把它们都录下来了
Okay, I got everything on video.
天 我以前从未见过这些
Oh, Jesus Christ, I didn't Even see these!
好 海瑟 够了 伙计 得走了
Okay, Heather, you got Enough, man. Let's go.
够了 别录了 够了
- That's enough! Stop taping!  - That's enough!
好 我们现在就走 走吧
- Okay, we're going right now.  - Let's go!
好 从这里出去 离开这
Okay, we're out of here. I'm leaving.
快点 关掉它!
Come on, turn it off!
救命啊
Help!
救救我们啊
Please help us!
像这样 我们不可能出得去的
We won't get out of here like that.
靠
Fuck!
我想我只能说我们迷路了
I think I can say that we're now lost.
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what to do.
我们可以都进到帐篷里来
We should all get Inside the tent.
好的
All right.
今晚我们就别升火了
Let's not light a fire tonight.
好的 我也是这样想的
Yeah, that's my thinking.
好主意 我们第一晚就没有升火
- That's a good idea.  - We didn't light one the first night.
然后什么都没发生
And nothing happened.
我们一升火 他们就知道了 没人跟着我们
We light fires, and they know. No one was following us.
我们最好把灯也关了
We should turn that light off, too.
好的
All right.
说实话 没什么可以吸引他们注意的了
Seriously, anything could attract them.
我们睡觉好了
Let's just go to sleep.
噢 天啊
Oh God.
把这拿出去
Put this out.
天哪 开玩笑 噢 天啊!
Jesus Christ, little kids. Oh, God!
我要穿上牛仔裤
I'm gonna put my jeans on.
拿走摄像机
Take the video camera. No, the DAT.
我要把这拍下来
I'm gonna get this on video.
哦 我的天 天啊
Oh, dear God, dear God!
走 快跑
Go, fucking go!
哦 天啊
Oh God!
快点
Hurry up!
我来了 我的鞋没绑好
I'm coming! My boots aren't laced!
我的天 那是什么啊?
Oh my God, what the fuck is that?
到底是什么啊?
What the fuck is that?
噢 妈的
Oh, shit!
迈克 你在哪 伙计?
Mike, where are you, man?
关上灯
Turn the lights off...
把灯关上 关上 乔什
...turn that light off. turn it off, Josh.
都关了 都关了
All lights off, all lights off.
我湿透了
I'm soaking.
好的
That's okay.
那是什么啊?
What was that?
那混蛋来了吗?
What the fuck is going on?
你听见了小孩的笑声了吗?
You hear that baby screaming?
闭嘴 没有什么小孩
Shut the fuck up. There's no fucking baby.
有 没有什么小孩
- Yes there was.  - There was no fucking baby.
我逃跑的时候什么也没听见
I haven't heard anything since we ran away...
天啊 好冷啊
Oh my God, it's cold.
我们快些 好吗?
We should be quiet, okay?
我什么也听不见了 我们走回去吧
I don't hear anything anymore. Let's go back.
我们在这多长时间了?
How long have we been here?
我不知道 伙计 一小时?
I don't know, man, an hour...?
太阳升起来了 我们没事了
The sun's up. We're okay now.
我们回去吧 整理好就走
Let's just get back, pack up, and go.
好的
Okay.
这是什么伙计?
What the fuck, man?
我的包呢?
Where's my pack?
在这 我的呢?
Right there. Where's mine?
这是什么伙计?
What the fuck, man?
他们为什么要这样?
Why're they fucking with us like this?
他们只是打开而已
They just opened it up.
他们倒光了我的水
They spilled all my water!
看上去很粘 伙计
Looks like slime, man.
这是水 伙计
It's just water, man.
是很粘 这他妈的是什么?
It is slime. What the fuck is it?
我们离开这
Let's get out of here.
海瑟 把那玩意关上吧 我们走
- Heather, turn that thing off!  - Let's go.
好的
Okay.
我对什么都不感兴趣了 走吧
I'm not interested anymore! Let's go!
我知道
I know.
那么就关上它
So turn it off.
镇定点 我们不在这带些什么走吗?
Relax. Have we got everything here?
比如狗屎 谁的包被打开了?
- Like I give a shit.  - Whose bag was opened?
是我的
It was mine!
为什么是你的?
Why you?
还没被吓够吗?
Are you not scared enough yet?
但为什么是你的?
But why you?
把它放下 这不是开玩笑
Put it down. This is not funny.
你认为我是在笑话这些?
Am I laughing at all?
不 你仍然在做着记录片 伙计
No, but you're still doing your documentary thing, man!
那该死的记录片
Still your fucking documentary!
别碰它 把那该死的东西关掉!
- Don't touch it!  - Then turn the goddam thing off!
如果你再惹火我 我会把你丢到河里
If you bite me again, I'll throw you in river.
别碰我的摄像机 关掉它!
- Don't touch my camera.  - Turn it off!
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我不是那个意思 明白?
I didn't mean it, okay?
你还好吗? 我还好
You all right?
好 我想回家
Yeah. I wanna go home...
但我不知道我们该怎样做
...but I wanna get what we can.
那是什么?
What the fuck...?
怎么可能?
Is this possible?
好的
All right.
我走在这
Here I go.
我讨厌走在小溪上的伐木
I hate crossing streams on logs.
如果不再走小溪上的伐木
If I never cross another stream...
的话 我会高兴死的
...on a log, I'll die happy.
我明白你为什么那么喜欢摄像机
I see why you like the video camera so much.
你知道?
You do?
我不是很确定
It's not quite reality.
我是想说我们该走了
Reality says we gotta move.
但它把真实的都去掉了 伙计
But it's a totally filtered reality, man.
就好像什么都并不都真实一样
As if everything's not quite the way it is.
让他单独待会儿
Just leave him alone awhile
我们得走了
We need to go.
离开他5分钟
Leave him for five minutes.
让他单独待会儿 5分钟就好
Leave him alone. Five minutes.
快 他很迷惑
Come on, he's lost it.
我知道 但是我们都很迷惑
I know, but we've all nearly lost it.
我知道 我们得互相照顾
I know, but we got to look after each other.
但我们不能照顾他
And we're not looking after him...
如果在他哭的时候拍他
...if we film him while he's crying.
我知道
I know.
我知道你懂
I know you know.
让我们努力保持冷静
Let's try and keep our wits.
但我们得走了
But we have to go.
好 相信我 我知道
Sure. Believe me, I know.
这很难保持平静
It's hard to stay calm.
我们得出去 知道
- We need to get out.  - I know.
我不知道的你什么也没告诉我
You're not telling me anything new,
只让他镇定
Just let him calm down.
谁有烟?
Anybody got a cigarette?
没有 伙计
No, man.
没有 什么也没有
No, there's none left.
没人有烟?
Nobody has any cigarettes?
都没有
We're out.
为什么
Why the fuck...
这都他妈的那么多狗屎?
...was this blue jelly shit on my shit?
走吧
Let's go.
如果一直向南走 我们就会出去了
If we keep going south, we'll get out.
求你了
Please...
我他妈再也不想晚上露营了
I don't wanna camp another fucking night.
乔什 我们都不想
Josh, none of us do.
我知道你不想
I know you don't.
无论谁 都想回去 这是事实
Whoever it is, is gonna come back, and that's a fact.
这不是事实
It's not a fact.
我们跑了三个晚上 一次比一次坏
It came three nights running, and it's worse every night.
这就是我想听的
Just what I need to hear right now.
我只想理智的说
I'm just trying to rationally say that...
以我们现在的速度 他们会永远跟着我们
...with our walking speed, they might just go on forever...
这不可能
Not possible in this country.
为什么不可能?
Why not?
因为我们美国毁了很多的森林
Because we've destroyed most of our woods in America.
让我们继续走 America America
- Let's just keep going.  - America, America...
God shed your grace on thee
...God shed your grace on thee...
Once so proudly we hailed
...Once so proudly we hailed...
at twilight's last gleaming
...at twilight's last gleaming...
这是我们走过的那棵树
That's the tree we crossed.
那树倒了 一模一样
That tree is down. Same one.
哦 天啊
Oh God!
噢 不
Oh no...
你在开玩笑 真是笑话
You got to be kidding, this is a joke!
这一点不好笑
It's not funny!
迈克 求你停下 停下
Mike, please stop... please stop...
哦 不
Oh no!
不 迈克 不是那棵!
No, Mike, it's not the same log!
是 看 不是的
- Same log!  - Look, it's not!
是的 好好看看
Yes it is! Open your eyes!
这不是那棵
It's not the same log...
一模一样
It's the same log.
我靠 天啊
Fuck you, God!!
一模一样
It's the same log.
好了 好了
Okay, it's okay.
你们想在哪扎营?
Where do you wanna camp?
向南走没用 明天我们向东走
Going south didn't work. Tomorrow we go east.
我不知道该说什么 乔什
I don't know what to say, Josh.
什么怪风把我们吹回了同一个地方?
How the fuck did we wind up in the same place?
我们整天都在向南走
We walked south all fucking day!
我不知道我们会在这
I don't know how we ended up here!
你还指望我干什么 还是说些什么?
Do you expect me to do, or say something?
你想怎么样?
What do you wanna do?
乔什?
Josh?
我想拍电影 海瑟
I wanna make movies, Heather.
这不是我们来的原因吗?
Isn't that why we came?
来拍电影的
Let's make some movies.
去你的
Fuck you.
别吵架好吗?
Let's not fight, please?
我不能断定 我是不是不会吵
...I can't take it. I can't fight.
我们有矛盾 是的 但请不要吵了
We're screwed, and that's it. Please stop fighting.
我来第一个放风
I'll do the first watch.
我第一个放风
I got first watch.
我们做的应该更好
It's not the time or place, guys.
我们还有事情准备
We have things to prepare for.
好 这就是你的动机
Okay, here's your motivation...
你很迷惑 你很生气有没人帮你
...you're lost, you're angry and no one's here to help you...
这里有个女巫
...there's a fucking witch who keeps leaving shit around...
没人能救你
...no one can help you...
她留下一些小玩意 你他妈就一个个拣起来
...she left little trinkets, and you fucking took one...
她在耍我们 没人能帮你
...she's chasing us. And no one can help you!
我们今天走了15个小时
We walked fifteen hours today...
我们会死在同一个地方
...and we ended up in the same place!
这儿没人能帮你 这就是你的动机
There's no one to help you! That's your motivation!
请不要说了
Please stop.
乔什 得了 她已经受够了
Josh, quit it. She's had enough.
你带她回来的干的不错
You got her back. Good one.
不 她还在拍电影
No, she's still making movies!
请不要说了 还在拍呢
- Please stop.  - Still making movies.
这都是我的不好 还不行吗? 请不要再说了
It's all I have left, okay? Just please stop.
不要对我吼
Please stop yelling at me.
我对整天哭都厌倦了
I'm fucking tired of crying all day.
我们得仔细思考 我们做了什么
We gotta think like human beings. We got things to do.
我们得想些办法 我们有很多要做
We've gotta do shifts. We got lots to do.
你不想要写下一个愉快的结尾 海瑟?
You gonna write us a happy ending, Heather?
好了 关掉它吧
Come on, turn it off.
你变得和她一样
You're getting like she was.
我不知道你怎么能缝好它伙计
I don't know how you can sew at this point, man,
好 我好冷
Well, I'm cold.
我知道 我听你的
- I know.  - I hear you.
我们又变好了 算是个小小的安慰
The smallest comforts we can get are good.
这看上去不是很可笑？ 虽然在这点上
Doesn't it seem absurd, though, at this point?
是的 是这样的
Yes, it does.
很多东西看上去都很可笑
Lots of things seem absurd.
就像昨晚我们睡觉时发生的事
Like sleeping where we were last night is freaking...
那很糟糕 那时
It's just fucking me up, period.
真的很糟糕 伙计
Really fucking me up, man.
抱歉 伙计 我也是 现在好了
- I'm sorry, man.  - Me too. It's all right.
抱歉 海瑟
I'm sorry, Heather.
没事了
It's all right.
谁想要夹心奶酪三明治?
Who wants a cheeseburger?
我 我想要
I do, I do...
我包里有夹心奶酪三明治
I got a cheeseburger in my pocket.
真的? 能照着让我切三明治吗?
Do you? Can I have a light to cut this?
知道我喜欢什么吗?
Know what I'd fucking love?
什么?
What?
马铃薯泥
Mashed potatoes.
我也是
Me too.
我妈妈做的马铃薯泥
My mom's mashed potatoes.
你很快就可以再吃到它们了
You'll have them again very soon.
马铃薯泥和半边屁股
Mashed potatoes and a piece of ass.
乔什?
Josh?
妈的 我们从来没离开得那么远!
Fuck, we never go out of earshot!
别急 镇定点
Come on, calm down.
我能吗?
How can I?
他大概在河那边
He's probably at the river.
如果在那儿 他能听见的
If he was there, he could hear me.
等他的回答
Wait for him to respond.
还记得他昨天说了什么吗？
Remember what he said yesterday?
说了什么?
What?
他包里的东西
About the shit on his bag.
走 我们去找他快
Let's go. We've gotta find him. Come on.
我们连车都找不到 怎么去找乔什啊?
If we can't even find the car, how are we gonna find Josh?
快点
Come on.
不 我还行
No, I'm fine.
来 来 放松点
Come on, come on, relax.
好的 一边收拾帐篷
All right, let's take down the tent...
一边等他回来 他会回来的
...and when he's back, we'll go.
我拿不定主意 迈克
I'm losing my mind, Mike.
乔什 不会回来了
Josh hasn't come back.
海瑟?
Heather?
我在这 迈克
I'm here, Mike.
我不知道如果 乔什 不在了
I don't know if Josh ran off.
他的东西在这
All his shit's here.
我拿着摄像机
I've got the camera...
我不知道我怎么能拿着摄像机走
...I don't know how I'm gonna hike with the camera.
你确定你扛摄像机?
Sure you wanna take it?
我们必须带上
We have to take the camera.
你觉得方向对吗?
How do you feel about east?
你觉得呢?
好吧 走南边没有用
Well, south didn't work.
哪里的巫婆更坏 东方的还是西方的?
Which witch was worse, the one from the east or from the south?
西方的
The witch of the west was the bad one.
那就走东边
Let's go east.
那该死的是什么?
What the hell is that?
乔什?
Josh?
我们得放下帐篷
We'll have to put up the tent.
我像个笨蛋
I'd like a meatball.
只是个笨蛋?
Just one meatball?
想有一大杯红酒
And a big glass of red wine.
是的 我想要一大瓶波尔多葡萄酒
Yeah, I would like a whole fucking bottle of Bordeaux.
还有一包烟
And a pack of smokes.
很好 好要好好洗个热水澡
That'd be good. and a long, hot bath.
还有一个大南瓜饼
And a big pumpkin pie.
南瓜饼和冰激淋?
A pumpkin pie with ice cream?
奶糖冰激淋?
Warm with milky ice cream?
是的 听上去不错
Yeah, sounds good.
你星期天喜欢干什么?
What do you like to do on a Sunday?
我时常开车去森林里徒步旅行
I used to like to drive to the woods and go hiking.
但我想现在不是了
But I think that might change now.
我想你会改掉的
I think you could scratch that.
打开门好吗?
Should we open the door?
这是恶作剧?
Is it a trick?
乔什
Josh!
那声音从哪来的?
Where's it coming from?
乔什 你在哪? 告诉我你在哪
Josh, where are you? Tell me where you are!
噢 上帝啊 不
Oh my God, no.
你觉得会不会又是他们?
Do you think that's them again?
在那儿?
Is it over here?
不 在那边
No, it's over here.
我们去找他
We'll look for him.
我不知道他是不是真在那儿
I don't know if it's really him.
我不知道去哪找
I don't even know where to look.
告诉我你在哪 乔什
Tell me where you are, Josh!
迈克?
Mike?
什么? 别睡熟了
- What?  - Please don't fall asleep.
我没有睡熟
I can't fall asleep.
无论怎么样 乔什 死定了
Whatever it is, it knows Josh has gone.
如果是 乔什 他会说他在哪的
If that was Josh, he would've said where he was.
无论怎么样 那听上去是乔什
Whatever it was, it sounded like Josh.
看见了吗?
See?
我只想让你知道 迈克在这里
I just want to show you that Mike's here.
在这 他在睡觉
There. He's sleeping.
噢 该死
Oh, shit.
这该死的是什么东西?
What the hell is that?
迈克 什么?
- Mike.  - What?
有什么东西在这里
There's something out here.
好的
Okay,
我要把它从帐篷门口拿开
I'm gonna move it from in front of the tent.
拿掉它 好的
- Get rid of it.  - Okay.
我把它从门口拿开
I'm taking it away from the tent.
我只想把它丢开
I'm just throwing it.
我们会继续走下去 是吗？
We'll just keep walking, okay.
好的
Okay.
我在我的包底下找到一些香烟
I found some cigarettes at the bottom of my pack...
如果我们还能抽烟 那我们就还活着
...so if we're smoking, we're still alive.
这上面都是血
It's all full of blood.
妈的 妈的 妈的
Shit, shit, shit!
上帝啊
Oh my God!
好了看见了?
Okay, see...?
是吗?
Yeah?
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
只是在洗手
Just washing my hands!
什么?
What?
只是在洗手
Just washing my hands!
我没事
I'm fine.
我想戴上手套
I'm gonna put my gloves on.
你还好吗?
You all right?
我还好 还好
I'm okay, I'm okay.
需要帮忙吗?
You need help?
不 我不需要任何帮助
No, I don't need any help.
我没事
I'm okay.
发生什么事了?
What happened?
没事 我只是又累又饿
Nothing. I'm just very hungry and very tired...
又害怕 我只想回家 好吗?
...and very scared, and I just wanna go home, okay?
好的
Okay.
我很好 我们都没事
But I'm fine, and we're okay.
噢 我的头发钩住了
Ow! My hair's caught.
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you, thank you.
好了 好了
Okay, okay.
2130个游戏
Two thousand one hundred thirty games...
我是国王!
...one more season and Cal Ripken is king!
我看不见它
And I won't see it...
因为我在森林里
...because I'll be in the woods.
别告诉我你吃干树叶
Tell me you're not eating a dry leaf.
我想向
I just want to apologize...
迈克的妈妈
...to Mike's mom...
还有乔什的妈妈道歉
...and Josh's mom...
还有我的妈妈道歉
...and my mom...
我对每个人感到抱歉
...and I'm sorry to everyone...
我太天真了
...I was very na?ve.
真是十分十分抱歉
I am so, so, sorry...
为发生的一切感到抱歉
...for everything that's happened...
因为不管现在迈克说什么
...because in spite of what Mike says now...
这都是我的错
...it was my fault...
因为这是我的主意
...because it was my project...
还有我的坚持
...and I insisted...
在这一切上的坚持
...insisted on everything.
我坚持说我们没有迷路
I insisted we weren't lost...
我坚持走下去
...I insisted we keep going...
坚持向南走
...I insisted we walk south.
每件事都被我坏了
Everything had to be my way.
我们会就这么死掉
And this is how we've ended up.
因为我们在这里
And it's all because of me that we're here now...
又冷又饿
...hungry and cold...
还受了伤
...and hunted.
我爱你 妈妈
I love you, mom...
爸爸
...dad...
很对不起
...I am so sorry.
那是什么?
...what was that?
我恐惧地闭上双眼
I'm scared to close my eyes...
又恐惧得打开它们
...and scared to open them.
噢 天呐
Oh God...
我们就要死了
...we're gonna die here.
你找到了吗? 你准备好了?
- You got it?  - You ready?
噢 天啊
Oh, Jesus Christ.
你准备好了没?
You ready?
给 拿着灯
Here, take this light.
那不可能是他
That can't be him.
该死 有座房子
Holy shit, it's a house.
注意看你脚下 该死 该死
- Watch your step.  - Holy shit, Holy shit...
乔什?
Josh?
迈克 迈克
Mike. Mike.
来啊
Come on.
迈克 你他妈在哪?
Mike, where the fuck are you?
来啊 我在房子里
Come on, I'm in the house!
迈克 别进去 求你了！
Mike, don't go in there, please!
迈克 求你了！ 迈克 你在哪?
Mike, please! Mike, where are you?
就在这
I'm right here!
他在哪?
Where is he?
迈克 不要
Mike, please don't.
他进了这?
Is he in here?
不
No.
哦 天
Oh, Jesus.
他在哪?
Where is he?
你要上楼吗?
Are you gonna go upstairs?
我听到他的声音了
I hear him. I hear him.
我听见你在那了 乔什
I hear you. Josh!
我要上楼
I'm going upstairs.
噢 上帝 噢
Oh, God, oh.
听见了吗?
Hear that?
他在哪?
Where is he?
你在哪?
Where are you?
过来
Come on!
我要下楼去
I'm getting downstairs.
快 我听见他的声音了 下楼！
Come on, I hear him, downstairs!
迈克
Mike!
快
Come on!
迈克
Mike!
乔什
Josh!
等下
Wait!
乔什 你在那里吗?
Josh, is that you down there?